<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title><![CDATA[PHOTOGRAPHY EVENTS ]]></title>
        <description><![CDATA[PHOTOGRAPHY EVENTS ]]></description>
        <link>https://thegrid.ai/safari-eye/</link>
        <generator>The Grid</generator>
        <lastBuildDate>Tue, 09 Aug 2016 21:46:32 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <atom:link href="https://thegrid.ai/safari-eye/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[No title]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://the-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/23ca9a4d-47d0-43a1-86e0-1e2a9c0d41a4.png">]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/safari-eye/photography-events/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">cf51959d-13f9-4f95-bf96-e1111679812e</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 19 May 2016 13:16:25 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[No title]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<p>For more information and check out what workshops are currently on offer.</p>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/safari-eye/for-more-information-and-check-out-what-workshops-are-curren/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">00437818-269f-4143-8353-9e5016dfb07b</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 09 Aug 2016 21:46:30 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[No title]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<p>Fancy yourself a bit of a photographer? Think you have an eye for what looks great on camera? Itching to get shooting but not quite sure how to get started in the commercial world? SafariEye could have just what you’re after! Our photography workshops provide the set, the lighting, the models, the product, and all you have to do is turn up with your camera and shoot! You can literally walk into a mock-commercial scenario where YOU are in charge of photography. Imagination abounds – perhaps a roaring 20’s Great Gatsby theme, or an exotic tropical island shoot, or maybe something more adventurous like letting us bring the wild heart of Africa to you!You bring your camera and materials, and we do the rest. It’s that easy. Our workshops also invite an industry professional guest - it may be a stylist to share some handy tips, or might be a director or industry photographer to pass on their knowledge – each workshop is different. SafariEye caters for beginners through to the more accomplished photographer, basically anyone with a passion for taking pictures!Come and experiment with your creativity, make a mock-ad, meet new people and network, challenge yourself, learn, laugh, get inspired, explore new ideas in a supportive environment - all whilst having HEAPS of fun! For more information and check out what workshops are currently on offer. </p>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/safari-eye/fancy-yourself-a-bit-of-a-photographer-think-you-have-an-ey/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">8e7d1e3c-f6f3-4673-afb4-22ada27b84fb</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 09 Aug 2016 21:43:51 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>